Ending
Hello everyone.
This is Sakura Kawasaki.
This project is Sakura Kawasaki's ASMR!
Crackle, crackle, crackle!
Just a year ago, I was at a meeting to show off my special skills.
I showed off my special skills
I showed off my ASMR skills!
This time, I had a long-cherished wish
I'd like to do a real ASMR this time.
I'd like to eat as soon as possible.
I don't know what I'm going to do.
Well then...
This...
They're stuck together.
This one's gone.
Ta-da!
Strawberry candy.
That's great!
I'm going to eat it!
Enjoy the next one!
Yes, it's delicious!
What is it?
It's so surreal!
I'm going to eat another one.
Delicious!
I'd like to try the grape candy too.
Bon appétit!
Mmm.
It's amazing!
It's really crunchy!
I'd like to try these potato chips next!
I think I like this sound better.
I think it sounds prettier.
It sounds prettier.
Strawberry is prettier.
Delicious.
Next.
Apples.
Bon appétit!
See you in the next video.
Bye.
Delicious!
Delicious.
Okay, next.
Macarons.
I'm so happy.
As usual.
It tastes good.
Delicious.
A little bit
It tastes like a fashionable
I'll have this one.
What flavor is it?
It's more chocolate.
What is it?
Berry?
It tastes like raspberries.
It tastes good.
I'd like to try some popcorn.
Do you hear that?
This might sound good.
I like it best when it comes from the bread lady.
This one.
It's so good.
Thanks for watching!
See you in the next video!
Can you hear me? This one.
Surprisingly silent, isn't it?
I don't know, maybe it doesn't make a sound.
Does it sound like it's going to make a sound?
Kimchi.
This is the ASMR I've been looking for.
It's the best sound I've heard all day.
Let's go with something with a lot of Chinese cabbage.
This is so good!
Let's try this too!
See you in the next video.
See you soon!
It's getting spicy!
And I love kimchi so much.
You know...
When I was little
I lived on kimchi, natto and rice
I used to live on kimchi and natto and rice.
This way.
Cute!
Cherry blossoms
Cute
Cherry blossoms on the link
I'll be back next time with more delicious food~!
Thanks for watching to the end.
I love you.
Don't you serve it so well?
It tastes so good!
My mouth is so sweet.
I'm going to eat this one more time.
I've eaten a bag or two or three in my day.
Big news!BIG NEWS.
So my first project was ASMR!
I've really been living my dream to do a real ASMR one.
I'm really happy from the bottom of my heart to see my dream come true like this today!
So, I would like to do my usual thing at the end
Bon appétit!
I hate it so much!
Mr. Sakutan
Shower shower
Bye bye!
Subscribe to our channel
Please give us a high rating!
Thank you all for the many requests for words you would like me to whisper!
I was so happy to see that you sent over 1,000!
Now, let's get started!
Listen to Sakura's voice.
Don't be smiling!
You idiot!
Are you sleeping, big brother?
Wake up, wake up!
You keep playing Sukura all the time.
You know what I'm talking about?
Triple axel, double dollop, double rope...
Three in a row.
One hessian.
Two doejays.
Three goatsbeard.
Four hetsji.
Five goji
Six goji
Seven hetsji.
Good night.
You're always working so hard.
You're really, really
You're really good at what you do.
Bye, bye, bye.